{
  "1": {
    "question": "What product(s)/service(s) does/do your company offer?",
    "choices": [
      "Fast-selling consumer goods (e.g. food, drink, confectionery products)",
      "Consumer durables (e.g. furniture, hi-fi, appliances)",
      "Industrial consumables or durables (e.g. raw materials, components, machinery, etc.)",
      "Services (e.g. financial, creative, training)"
    ],
    "answers": [3, 3, 3, 3],
    "info": {
      "text": "AGOA industry sectors",
      "link": "https://agoa.info/toolkit/industry-sectors.html"
    }
  },
  "2": {
    "question": "How long are you in the business?",
    "choices": [
      "More then 15 years",
      "Less then one year",
      "Between one and three years",
      "More then three years"
    ],
    "answers": [5, 0, 1, 3]
  },
  "3": {
    "question": "Is the trend of sales an inquiries up or down",
    "choices": ["Up", "Down", "About the same", "Don't know"],
    "answers": [5, 0, 1, 0]
  },
  "4": {
    "question": "How many sales offices, sales locations, or distribution points does your company have?",
    "choices": [
      "One or more domestic offices and at least one foreign office",
      "One",
      "Two",
      "More then two"
    ],
    "answers": [5, 0, 1, 3]
  },
  "5": {
    "question": "For what timeframe is your company’s business plan",
    "choices": ["Six months", "One year", "Three years", "No business plan"],
    "answers": [-30, 1, 4, -50]
  },
  "6": {
    "question": "Have you exported before",
    "choices": [
      "Yes",
      "No"
    ],
    "answers": [5, 0]
  },
  "7": {
    "question": "How much time is your company going to dedicate to export planning",
    "choices": [
      "Considerable planning efforts (three to six months)",
      "Some (one to two months)",
      "Minimal (less than a month)",
      "Don't know"
    ],
    "answers": [7, 1, -15, -15]
  },
  "8": {
    "question": "How quickly does management expect export operations to become self-sustaining?",
    "choices": [
      "Three years",
      "Immediately",
      "Six months",
      "Don't know"
    ],
    "answers": [-2, 1, 2, -0]
  },
  "9": {
    "question": "Has your company's management allocated (or re-allocated) resources for the export effort?",
    "choices": [
      "Assigned extra personnel only",
      "Allocated extra financial resources",
      "Allocated both personnel and financial resources",
      "No extra resources will be allocated"
    ],
    "answers": [2, 3, 5, 0]
  },
  "10": {
    "question": "Which of the following U.S. market entry barriers have you researched?",
    "choices": [
      "Tariffs and non-tariff barriers",
      "International standards",
      "Product modification",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answers": [0, 0, 0, 5]
  },
  "11": {
    "question": "When you were setting the US price for your product/service, what did you take into account?",
    "choices": [
      "Costs only",
      "Market demand and Costs only",
      "Competition and Costs only",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answers": [0, 0, 0, 5]
  },
  "12": {
    "question": "Have you decided on your preferred methods of payment for your export quotations?",
    "choices": [
      "Yes",
      "No"
    ],
    "answers": [2, 0]
  },
  "13": {
    "question": "What does your U. S. market analyses include of the following?",
    "choices": [
      "Structure",
      "Market share and size",
      "None of the above",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answers": [1, 1, 0, 5]
  },
  "14": {
    "question": "Have you decided on what distribution channels will you use in the US?",
    "choices": [
      "Yes",
      "No"
    ],
    "answers": [3, 0]
  },
  "15": {
    "question": "Do you have a clear idea of the mix of promotional methods that will be used in the US",
    "choices": [
      "Yes",
      "No"
    ],
    "answers": [3, 0]
  },
  "16": {
    "question": "Do you have promotional materials in English language?",
    "choices": [
      "Yes",
      "No"
    ],
    "answers": [5, 0]
  },
  "17": {
    "question": "Do you have a website in English language?",
    "choices": [
      "Yes",
      "No"
    ],
    "answers": [5, 0]
  },
  "18": {
    "question": "With how many countries has business been conducted?",
    "choices": [
      "None",
      "One",
      "Between two and three",
      "More then three"
    ],
    "answers": [0, 1, 2, 3]
  },
  "19": {
    "question": "Have you already discussed exporting to the U.S. with other companies that are already experienced on the U.S. market?",
    "choices": [
      "Yes",
      "No"
    ],
    "answers": [5, 0]
  },
  "20": {
    "question": "Have you participated in international trade shows in the U.S.?",
    "choices": [
      "Never",
      "Once as an attendee",
      "Two and more as an attendee",
      "More then once as an attendee & at least once as an exhibitor"
    ],
    "answers": [0, 1, 2, 5]
  },
  "21": {
    "question": "How much international business experience does your staff have, either/both in theory and/or practice?",
    "choices": [
      "None",
      "Moderate amount",
      "Considerable amount",
      "Don't know"
    ],
    "answers": [1, 2, 3, 0]
  },
  "22": {
    "question": "Which of your company’s employees speak English?",
    "choices": [
      "Top management only",
      "Middle management and A",
      "Administrative staff and A and B",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answers": [2, 3, 4, 0]
  },
  "23": {
    "question": "Did your company succeeded in obtaining a bank loan in the last 10 years?",
    "choices": [
      "Yes",
      "No",
      "Don't know"
    ],
    "answers": [5, 0, 0]
  },
  "24": {
    "question": "What method of payment do you consider the least secure?",
    "choices": [
      "Open account",
      "Cash in advance",
      "Letter of credit",
      "Documentary collection"
    ],
    "answers": [5, 0, 0, 0]
  },
  "25": {
    "question": "How is your company using e-mail communication method?",
    "choices": [
      "External communication only.",
      "Internal communication only.",
      "Both as internal & external communication method",
      "Not used at all"
    ],
    "answers": [2, 2, 5, 0]
  }
}
